On the last episode, we used Python to compute the Mell frequency sepstral coefficients, or MFCCs, of the audio files found in the Google Speech Commands data set.
在上集节目中，我们使用Python计算了音频文件的梅尔频率倒谱系数（MFCCs），这些文件来自Google语音命令数据集。
We also divided these features and labels up into training, validation, and test sets.
我们还将这些特征和标签分成了训练集、验证集和测试集。
Now we're ready to train our neural network.
现在我们准备训练我们的神经网络。
When we think of training a model on command words, we might think of having the model recognize one of many different words.
当我们想到训练一个模型来识别命令词时，我们可能会想到让模型识别许多不同的词语中的一个。
So if we said stop, our algorithm would compute the MFCCs of that word and send those coefficients as features to our model.
因此，如果我们说“停”，我们的算法将计算该词的MFCCs，并将这些系数作为特征发送到我们的模型。
The model would then make a prediction based on those features and tell us that it thinks we said stop out of all the possible wake words it knows.
然后模型会根据这些特征做出预测，并告诉我们它认为我们在所有可能的唤醒词中说的是“停”。
While this might be useful in some scenarios, such as giving commands to a robot,
虽然这在某些场景中可能有用，比如给机器人下达命令，
it's very computationally expensive to compute the probabilities of all the different words.
但计算所有不同词语的概率非常耗费计算资源。
Since we only care about one word, it's much easier to train a binary classifier to recognize that one word and bundle every other sound and word into a single category.
由于我们只关心一个词，训练一个二分类器来识别这个词并将其他所有声音和词汇归为一个类别要容易得多。
Our two categories will be stop and not stop.
我们的两个类别将是“停”和“不是停”。
Making a prediction with the model will then give us the probability that it thinks it recognized the word stop from the MFCC features we give it.
使用模型进行预测时，将给出模型认为它识别出的MFCC特征中的词是“停”的概率。
If that probability is over some threshold, we'll have our program respond appropriately by, say, turning on a light.
如果该概率超过某个阈值，我们的程序将通过例如打开灯等方式作出相应的反应。
So that means we need to train a mathematical model that classifies sounds as either the spoken word stop or something else.
这意味着我们需要训练一个数学模型，将声音分类为说出的词是“停”或其他东西。
In a new notebook, let's load our modules.
在一个新的笔记本中，让我们加载我们的模块。
We'll need OS to deal with loading files.
我们需要使用OS模块来处理加载文件。
We'll also want layers and models from Keras to build our neural network.
我们还需要从Keras中获取层和模型来构建我们的神经网络。
Finally, we need NumPy to help us deal with matrices and other tensors.
最后，我们需要NumPy来帮助我们处理矩阵和其他张量。
As a quick test, let's read the words that are available to us from the data set, leaving off the background noise.
作为一个快速测试，让我们读取数据集中可用的词，去掉背景噪音。
Next, we'll set the path to our feature set file that we created in the last episode.
接下来，我们将设置在上集节目中创建的特征集文件的路径。
Additionally, we'll want to save our neural network model to a file when we're done, so
另外，当我们完成时，我们希望将我们的神经网络模型保存到一个文件中，
we'll set the file name here.
我们将在这里设置文件名。
We'll also define our wake word here.
我们还将在这里定义我们的唤醒词。
Note that it must be one of the ones listed from the available targets in the data set.
注意，它必须是数据集中列出的可用目标词之一。
We can then use NumPy to load the feature set file and print out the sets available to us.
然后我们可以使用NumPy加载特征集文件并打印出可用的集合。
Let's assign those to some variables for easier access.
让我们将它们分配给一些变量以便于访问。
A tensor is a collection of data arranged in any number of dimensions.
张量是按任意维度排列的数据集合。
A matrix is simply a two-dimensional tensor.
矩阵只是一个二维张量。
A grayscale image, like the ones we were creating with the MFCCs, is just a matrix.
像我们用MFCCs创建的灰度图像就是一个矩阵。
So if we have a collection of matrices ordered in a linear fashion, we've created a three-dimensional tensor.
所以，如果我们有一个线性排列的矩阵集合，我们就创建了一个三维张量。
If we look at the dimensions of the feature sets, we can see that the first dimension is the number of samples in that set.
如果我们查看特征集的维度，可以看到第一维是该集合中的样本数量。
And the other two dimensions are the number of coefficients and the number of sets of coefficients in each sample.
而其他两维是每个样本中系数的数量和系数集的数量。
If we look at one of the sets of labels, we can see that it's a collection of numbers that correspond to the different words.
如果我们查看标签集，可以看到它是一个对应于不同词汇的数字集合。
Zero is backward, one is bed, two is bird, and so on.
0是“向后”，1是“床”，2是“鸟”，等等。
We don't want that for a binary classifier.
我们不希望二分类器这样。
So we find the index of our target word, stop, and use NumPy's equal function to only keep the stop label.
所以我们找到目标词“停”的索引，并使用NumPy的equal函数只保留“停”标签。
Normally, this function returns true and false, so we'll want to translate them to one and zero using the asType function.
通常，该函数返回true和false，所以我们需要使用asType函数将它们转换为1和0。
I'll keep them as 64-bit floating point values, since that seems to be what they were originally stored as.
我会将它们保留为64位浮点值，因为这似乎是它们最初存储的格式。
If we look again, we see that the stop labels now have a one and everything else has a zero.
如果我们再看一次，可以看到“停”标签现在为1，其他所有标签为0。
Here's the tricky part.
这是难点。
There aren't as many ones in this set.
在这个集合中1的数量不多。
In fact, we can see that only about 4% of labels in the validation set are one.
事实上，我们可以看到验证集中只有约4%的标签为1。
That means if the model were to just give us the answer of not stop for everything,
这意味着如果模型只是告诉我们所有东西的答案都不是“停”，
it would be correct over 95% of the time.
它的正确率会超过95%。
So we need to do better than that if we hope to identify when someone says stop.
所以我们需要做得比这更好，如果我们希望识别出有人说“停”。
A convolutional neural network, which you'll often see abbreviated as ConvNet or CNN, seems to be one of the most popular methods for classifying images.
卷积神经网络（通常缩写为ConvNet或CNN）似乎是图像分类最流行的方法之一。
I'll be honest in that I don't fully understand the details of how a ConvNet works, but there lots of good resources out there if you want to learn more about them.
老实说，我并不完全理解卷积神经网络的工作细节，但如果你想了解更多关于它们的知识，有很多很好的资源。
For now, we just need to get something working.
目前，我们只需要让它工作。
I found a simple image classification network on this Geeks for Geeks tutorial that seems to give us okay accuracy, and it's easy to implement.
我在这个Geeks for Geeks教程中找到了一个简单的图像分类网络，它似乎给了我们不错的准确率，而且容易实现。
We'll start with that for our classifier.
我们将从这个分类器开始。
You are welcome to experiment with other networks too.
你也可以尝试其他网络。
Tweaking some of the weights in the VGG16 network seems to be pretty popular.
调整VGG16网络中的一些权重似乎也很流行。
Let's take a look at the network from that tutorial to get a basic idea of what's going A convolutional neural network usually consists of two different parts.
让我们看看教程中的网络，了解一下其基本原理。卷积神经网络通常由两个不同部分组成。
The first is the set of convolutional layers.
第一部分是卷积层组。
These layers act to automatically learn and extract features from the image.
这些层通过自动学习和提取图像特征来工作。
These features are then passed to a fully connected neural network that attempts to classify the image based on the features provided.
这些特征然后传递到一个全连接的神经网络，该网络试图根据提供的特征分类图像。
The first section of the convolutional set consists of three steps.
卷积集的第一部分由三个步骤组成。
The first step is the actual convolution operation.
第一步是实际的卷积操作。
It consists of moving a window across the whole image as a sort of filter in order to extract some features, such as detecting edges.
它由移动窗口作为一种滤波器遍历整个图像来提取一些特征，例如检测边缘。
This sliding window filter is known as a kernel and performs some math operations as it samples a set of pixels from the image.
这种滑动窗口滤波器被称为内核，它在采样图像的一组像素时执行一些数学运算。
In this example, the window is 2x2 pixels.
在这个例子中，窗口是2x2像素。
The weights used in this kernel are different for every node and are updated automatically during training.
这个内核中使用的权重在每个节点上是不同的，并在训练期间自动更新。
With this example, we have 32 nodes in the first convolutional layer.
在这个例子中，我们在第一个卷积层中有32个节点。
So we end up with 32 different filtered images that give us some fine details in the image, such as edges and corners.
因此，我们最终得到了32个不同的滤波图像，它们为我们提供了一些图像中的细节，例如边缘和角落。
The rectified linear unit, or ReLU activation, simply sets all negative numbers in the feature maps to zero.
修正线性单元（ReLU）激活简单地将特征图中的所有负数设置为零。
It adds a level of non-linearity to the nodes, which allows us to train the model.
它为节点增加了一定程度的非线性，这使我们能够训练模型。
We then perform a max pooling step, which in effect reduces the size of these feature maps by downsampling them.
然后我们执行最大池化步骤，实际上是通过下采样减少这些特征图的大小。
This helps the neural network identify where features are supposed to approximately be in the image instead of their exact locations.
这有助于神经网络识别图像中特征的大致位置，而不是它们的确切位置。
It also saves us some computations in the next layer.
这也为下一层节省了一些计算。
These steps make up the first layer.
这些步骤组成了第一层。
We repeat these steps for the second layer, which helps the network identify more complex features.
我们重复这些步骤来构建第二层，这有助于网络识别更复杂的特征。
In this network, we do this process one more time in the third layer.
在这个网络中，我们在第三层再做一次这个过程。
Notice that the final convolutional layer has 64 nodes instead of 32, so we end up with 64 two-dimensional maps of features.
注意，最终的卷积层有64个节点，而不是32个，所以我们最终得到了64个二维特征图。
These maps will be much smaller than the original image, mostly due to the max pooling steps that drastically reduce the size of the tensors in each layer.
这些特征图将比原始图像小得多，主要是由于最大池化步骤大大减少了每层张量的大小。
The final feature maps at the end of the convolutional layers will, ideally, be a collection of complex features that help us define the image.
卷积层结束时的最终特征图理想情况下将是一个复杂特征的集合，有助于我们定义图像。
For example, if we wanted to identify breeds of dogs, this might be pointed ears versus floppy ears.
例如，如果我们想识别狗的品种，这可能是尖耳朵与垂耳朵。
Our classifier network expects a one-dimensional tensor, or vector input, so we need to flatten our collection of two-dimensional tensors into one long string of numbers.
我们的分类器网络期望一个一维张量或向量输入，所以我们需要将我们的二维张量集合展开成一个长字符串的数字。
This vector is then fed into a rather shallow neural network in this example.
在这个例子中，这个向量被输入到一个相当浅的神经网络中。
The first layer is 64 fully connected nodes with the ReLU activation being used again.
第一层有64个全连接节点，仍然使用ReLU激活。
These nodes feed a final layer that is just one node.
这些节点连接到一个只有一个节点的最终层。
That node's activation is the sigmoid function, which is common in binary classifiers like this one.
该节点的激活函数是sigmoid函数，这在这种二分类器中很常见。
The output of this final node is a prediction of whether the input MFCC image was the word stop, or something else.
这个最终节点的输出是对输入的MFCC图像是否为词“停”或其他词的预测。
You'll notice that there is a dropout layer added between the two layers.
你会注意到在两层之间添加了一个dropout层。
A dropout layer randomly removes inputs to the next layer during training.
dropout层在训练期间随机删除下一层的输入。
It is an easy way to help prevent overfitting of the neural network.
这是防止神经网络过拟合的简单方法。
Note that the dropout layer should be disabled during testing and deployment, which Keras does by default.
注意，dropout层在测试和部署期间应禁用，Keras默认这样做。
Now that we have a broad understanding of what's going on in this ConvNet, let's head back to our program to implement it.
现在我们对卷积神经网络有了广泛的理解，让我们回到程序中实现它。
If we print out the dimensions of our XSETs, we can see that it's a collection of 16 by 16 arrays, with the first dimension being the index of the sample.
如果我们打印出X集合的维度，可以看到它是一个16x16数组的集合，第一维是样本的索引。
TensorFlow expects tensors in four dimensions as inputs to ConvNets.
TensorFlow期望输入到卷积神经网络的是四维张量。
Specifically, it wants sample number, height, width, and channel.
具体来说，它希望是样本数、高度、宽度和通道数。
Since ConvNets need to be able to handle color images,
由于卷积神经网络需要处理彩色图像，
you'll often see each sample composed of three sets of two-dimensional arrays,
你通常会看到每个样本由三组二维数组组成，
one for each red, green, and blue channel.
分别对应红色、绿色和蓝色通道。
However, our MFCCs only have one channel per sample.
但是，我们的MFCCs每个样本只有一个通道。
But we still need to feed the ConvNet four dimensions,
但我们仍然需要输入四维数据到卷积神经网络，
so we use the reshape function to add an extra dimension that doesn't hold any extra information.
所以我们使用reshape函数添加一个不包含任何额外信息的维度。
If we print out the shape of our input data, we can see that we have added the extra channel as the fourth dimension on these tensors.
如果我们打印出输入数据的形状，可以看到我们已经将额外的通道作为第四维度添加到这些张量中。
Just to check, we can see that one sample from our test set is a 16 by 16 array.
为了检查，我们可以看到测试集中的一个样本是一个16x16数组。
There's a third dimension, but since there's only one element, it's still basically a two-dimensional array.
有第三个维度，但由于只有一个元素，它基本上仍然是一个二维数组。
Now, we build the model using Keras.
现在，我们使用Keras构建模型。
This is the same model we found on that Geeks for Geeks tutorial.
这与我们在Geeks for Geeks教程中找到的模型相同。
We have three convolutional layers with ReLU activations and max pooling operations.
我们有三个带有ReLU激活和最大池化操作的卷积层。
The output of that gets fed into a fully connected, or dense, neural network with two layers.
这些输出进入一个由两层全连接神经网络。
The first has 64 nodes and the second has only one node that gives us a prediction of whether the provided MFCCs belong to the spoken word stop or something else.
第一层有64个节点，第二层只有一个节点，它给我们一个预测，MFCCs属于说出的词“停”或其他词。
We can use the summary function to print out an overview of the model.
我们可以使用summary函数打印出模型的概述。
When trying to optimize a model for execution speed, it can be useful to look at the total number of parameters.
在尝试优化模型的执行速度时，查看参数总数是有用的。
These are the number of weights or other parameters that can be trained in the model.
这些是模型中可以训练的权重或其他参数的数量。
And this number gives us an idea of how many math operations are needed to both train the model as well as use it for predictions.
这个数字给我们一个需要多少数学运算来训练和使用模型进行预测的概念。
Ideally, you want to get this number to be as low as possible by playing with the model's shape and size while still having the model make good predictions on the cross-validation set.
理想情况下，你希望通过调整模型的形状和大小将这个数字尽可能低，同时仍然能够在交叉验证集上做出良好的预测。
Next, we set up the model for training and give it some parameters.
接下来，我们设置模型训练并给它一些参数。
These values, along with some others, such as the size and shape of the MFCCs, make up a set known as the hyperparameters.
这些值以及其他一些值，例如MFCCs的大小和形状，组成了超参数集。
These values do not get automatically updated during the training of the model,
这些值在模型训练期间不会自动更新，
but you can adjust them manually to affect how the model performs.
但你可以手动调整它们以影响模型的表现。
We need to provide a loss function, which is how the model calculates how far away the prediction is from the actual value during training.
我们需要提供一个损失函数，这是模型在训练期间计算预测值与实际值之间距离的方法。
Because this is a binary classification problem with a sigmoid activation on the final node,
因为这是一个二分类问题，最终节点使用的是sigmoid激活，
we want to use binary cross entropy as our loss function.
所以我们希望使用二元交叉熵作为损失函数。
For optimizers, you'll see stochastic gradient descent, RMSProp, and Adam used very frequently with neural networks like this.
对于优化器，你会经常看到随机梯度下降、RMSProp和Adam在这种神经网络中使用。
The example we found uses RMSProp, so we'll go with that.
我们找到的示例使用了RMSProp，所以我们也使用它。
Feel free to try different optimizer functions to see how it affects training.
请随意尝试不同的优化器函数，看看它如何影响训练。
Finally, it can be helpful to record some metrics during training that we can plot later.
最后，在训练期间记录一些指标以便稍后绘图是有帮助的。
So we'll have it record accuracy, abbreviated ACC.
所以我们让它记录准确率，缩写为ACC。
Now that we have the model set up, it's time to train it.
现在我们有了模型设置，就可以训练它了。
We do that by calling the fit function, and we pass it our training samples along with the associated ground truth answers in the y vector.
我们通过调用fit函数来实现这一点，并传递我们的训练样本和y向量中的相应真实答案。
We tell it how many epochs we want to go through and give it a batch size.
我们告诉它我们希望经历多少个epoch并给它一个batch size。
Feel free to play around with both of these numbers to see if you can make it train faster or more accurately.
随意调整这些数字，看看是否可以加快训练速度或提高准确性。
Finally, we provide it the validation samples and answers.
最后，我们提供验证样本和答案。
We will want to look at how well the model performs on predicting unseen data as part of our accuracy measurement.
我们希望看到模型在预测未见数据时的表现作为准确度的一个部分。
Let's run this. It might take a few minutes.
让我们运行这个。可能需要几分钟。
When it's done, take a look at the output of the final epoch.
完成后，查看最终epoch的输出。
You should see an accuracy score, which tells you how well the model performed on training data
你应该看到一个准确率分数，它告诉你模型在训练数据上的表现，
and a validation accuracy score, which tells you how well the model performed on the cross validation data.
以及一个验证准确率分数，它告诉你模型在交叉验证数据上的表现。
Let's plot the accuracy and loss as functions of epochs.
让我们绘制准确率和损失随epoch变化的曲线。
We'll import Matplotlib and create two plots.
我们将导入Matplotlib并创建两个图。
The training accuracy is given by dots and the cross validation accuracy is given by the solid line.
训练准确率用点表示，交叉验证准确率用实线表示。
The training and validation loss and accuracy curves should all converge around separate values.
训练和验证损失和准确率曲线应都在各自值附近收敛。
If you see the curves still wildly swinging after a few epochs, it means something went wrong during training.
如果你看到曲线在几个epoch之后仍在大幅波动，说明训练过程中出了问题。
As you can see, our model did very well in the upper 90s, a little better than just guessing that the answer is not stop every time.
如你所见，我们的模型表现非常好，准确率在90%以上，比只是每次都猜“不是停”要好一点。
Most of the time, you will find that the model performs better on the training data than on the validation data after a number of epochs.
大多数情况下，你会发现模型在训练数据上的表现比在验证数据上更好，经过若干个epoch后更是如此。
This is because the model starts to learn features unique to the samples in the training set that do not generalize well to unseen data.
这是因为模型开始学习训练集中样本的独特特征，这些特征无法很好地推广到未见数据上。
This is known as overfitting and can cause problems when you deploy your model.
这被称为过拟合，当你部署模型时可能会造成问题。
Look for a large gap between training accuracy and validation accuracy, as well as a gap in the loss function to see if your model has been overfit to the training samples.
寻找训练准确率和验证准确率之间的大差距，以及损失函数上的差距，以确定你的模型是否过拟合了训练样本。
You might have to extract different features, use different model structures, or try different training parameters to find a model that does not overfit and generalizes well to unseen data.
你可能需要提取不同的特征，使用不同的模型结构，或尝试不同的训练参数，以找到一个不过拟合且能够很好地推广到未见数据上的模型。
Note that running the training step again, even with the same parameters and hyperparameters,
请注意，即使使用相同的参数和超参数再次运行训练步骤，
can produce different results, as the weights in the neural network are randomly initialized before training.
也可能产生不同的结果，因为神经网络中的权重在训练前是随机初始化的。
I think this model will work well enough for a first prototype.
我认为这个模型对于一个原型来说已经足够好了。
However, if you remember from the previous episode, we are only using 10% of the data for training and validation.
不过，如果你记得上集节目，我们只使用了10%的数据进行训练和验证。
This can be a useful subset if you want to tweak some of the model parameters and hyperparameters, like the MFCC calculations. but
如果你想调整一些模型参数和超参数（例如MFCC计算），这个子集可能会有用，但
since we're ready to test and hopefully deploy our model, we'll want to go back and run both the feature extraction and training scripts on all of the data.
既然我们准备好测试并希望部署我们的模型，我们就需要回去对所有数据运行特征提取和训练脚本。
Go back to the feature extraction script that we wrote in the last episode and change the keep samples percentage from 10% to 100%.
回到上集节目中编写的特征提取脚本，将保持样本百分比从10%更改为100%。
Now just run the script again.
现在重新运行脚本。
Note that feature extraction will take a much longer time, possibly an hour or two, depending on your computer.
注意，特征提取将花费更长时间，可能需要一个小时或更久，具体取决于你的计算机。
When that's done, we should have the full set of features stored in the NPZ file.
完成后，我们应该在NPZ文件中有完整的特征集。
So return to the classifier training script and run it again.
因此，返回分类器训练脚本并再次运行它。
Like with the feature extraction, training will take much longer, up to maybe an hour or so.
像特征提取一样，训练将花费更长时间，可能需要一个小时左右。
Because we're using all of the data this time, it should, in theory, produce a more robust model.
因为这次我们使用了所有数据，所以理论上应该产生一个更强大的模型。
When it's done plot the accuracy and loss curves again to make sure that they look reasonable.
完成后，再次绘制准确率和损失曲线，确保它们看起来合理。
Is the validation accuracy above the chance of just randomly guessing not stop?
验证准确率是否高于随机猜测“不是停”的机会？
And does it appear that our training did not overfit the model too much?
我们的训练是否没有过度拟合模型？
The last thing we need to do is save the model as a file, which we can do with the save model function.
我们最后需要做的是将模型保存为一个文件，我们可以使用save model函数来完成。
Note that we'll be saving it as wakeword stop model dot h5.
注意，我们将保存为wakeword stop model dot h5。
And we can load this model in TensorFlow if we want to make predictions on new data.
如果我们想在新数据上进行预测，可以在TensorFlow中加载这个模型。
Now that our model is done, we can test it using the test data that we set aside.
现在我们的模型完成了，我们可以使用预留的测试数据进行测试。
First, let's print out all of the indices for the training data that point to the word stop.
首先，让我们打印出所有指向“停”这个词的训练数据索引。
We load our model from the file and have it predict the output from 10 of the training samples around this index.
我们从文件中加载模型并让它预测这些索引附近的10个训练样本的输出。
Because we are using the sigmoid function for the final activation, the output of the essentially a confidence score of how much the model thinks the input is in the class stop as opposed to not stop.
由于我们使用的是sigmoid函数作为最终激活，输出实际上是模型认为输入属于“停”类别而不是“不是停”类别的置信度评分。
Generally, we would consider anything over point five as being our target wakeword or stop.
通常，我们会认为任何超过0.5的分数都是我们的目标唤醒词或“停”。
As you can see, the model should produce a confidence score that's above point five for samples that correspond to the word stop.
如你所见，对于对应“停”这个词的样本，模型应该会产生高于0.5的置信度评分。
However, it's not perfect.
然而，这并不完美。
You can easily find test samples that do not produce a predicted score above point five.
你可以很容易地找到不会产生高于0.5预测分数的测试样本。
And similarly, you can find examples in the not stop category that do produce a predicted score above point five.
同样地，你也可以在“不是停”类别中找到预测分数高于0.5的例子。
That being said, it seems to work well enough for a prototype model.
话虽如此，对于一个原型模型，它似乎工作得足够好了。
Finally, we can call the evaluate function using all of the test data, which will give us a loss score and any metrics that we ask the model to record, which is accuracy in this case.
最后，我们可以调用evaluate函数，使用所有测试数据，这将给我们一个损失评分和我们要求模型记录的任何指标，在这种情况下是准确率。
Ideally, this should give you something close to your validation accuracy.
理想情况下，这应该给你一个接近验证准确率的结果。
It seems that our model is about 98.4% accurate at predicting if a one second clip of audio contains the word stop.
看来我们的模型在预测一个一秒的音频片段中是否包含“停”这个词时准确率约为98.4%。
If the test accuracy is much less than the validation accuracy,
如果测试准确率远低于验证准确率，
it means that the model has been overfit to the validation data and you'll likely need to go back to the drawing board.
这意味着模型已过拟合到验证数据，你可能需要重新开始。
This is the number you would provide in a white paper or project report when asked about how the model performs on unseen data.
这是在白皮书或项目报告中被问及模型在未见数据上的表现时你会提供的数字。
Once again, I'm pretty happy with the performance of this model.
再次强调，我对这个模型的表现非常满意。
I hope this helps you get started training your own neural network.
希望这能帮助你开始训练自己的神经网络。
I know it's a lot to take in, but feel free to play around with some of the parameters and settings found in this example.
我知道这需要很多时间，但请随意尝试这个示例中的一些参数和设置。
On the next episode, we'll convert our saved model file to a TensorFlow Lite model file and then deploy it on a Raspberry Pi.
在下集节目中，我们将把我们的保存模型文件转换为TensorFlow Lite模型文件，然后将其部署在Raspberry Pi上。
This is the start of creating your very own Edge AI device
这是创建你自己的边缘AI设备的开始
See you then.
再见。